"而且这还是自然景观呢"
"Especially when you realize it's a natural thing."
什么 什么
What? What?
真不太妙
Oh, that's not good.
什么
What?
你是想告诉我
You mean to tell me
这女孩相信拉什莫尔山上
that this girl believes that the faces of our four presidents
出现四张总统脸的原因是
showed up on a mountain through the process of...
自然腐蚀
natural erosion?
是啊
Yeah!
风雨雕刻出了总统脸
Wind and rain carved out the presidents.
智慧有多种形式 麦肯齐
Many forms of intelligence, Mack.
我爱风和雨
I love wind and rain!
我的天
Oh, my God.
说实话 麦肯齐
Hey, honestly, Mack,
这女孩和你绝配
this girl is perfect for you, man.
简直天生一对
She's like a match made in heaven.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
我一夜都没睡
I haven't slept.
威特德 你在哪
Whitted, where you at?
就剩一点啦 马上搞定
We got a chain left to finish the mop-up.